<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<bookdepository>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Fast Exercise</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>FE</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dr Michael Mosley</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Dr Michael Mosley trained as a doctor before becoming a journalist and television presenter. He is the author of The Fast Diet, The 8-Week Blood Sugar Diet, The Clever Guts Diet and The Fast 800. He is married with four children. Dr Michael Mosley trained as a doctor before becoming a journalist and television presenter. He is the author of The Fast Diet, The 8-Week Blood Sugar Diet, The Clever Guts Diet and The Fast 800. He is married with four children.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fitness &amp; Diet</categorie>
        <bookSummary> The simple secret of high intensity training: get fitter, stronger and better toned in just a few minutes a day</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.79/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>208</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-12-19</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Short Books Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1780721986</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>781780721989</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>22679</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/7807/9781780721989.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>your name. The Official Visual Guide</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>YNOVG</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Makoto Shinkai</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Makoto Shinkai is a director, manga artist, and a writer known for works such as your name., The Garden of Words, and 5 Centimeters Per Second.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Graphic Novels, Anime &amp; Manga</categorie>
        <bookSummary>This story guide for Makoto
                    Shinkai's hit your name. features beautiful scenes from the film, along
                    with background art, character and concept art, storyboards, and a variety of
                    exclusive interviews from the people who brought Mitsuha and Taki's story to
                    life!</bookSummary>
        <rating>3/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>128</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-12-29</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Little, Brown &amp; Company</publisher>
        <locationCity>New York</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United States</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1975358716</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781975358716</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>778683</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/mid/9781/9753/9781975358716.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Circe</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>CIRCE</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Madeline Millert</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Madeline Miller is the author of The Song of Achilles, which won the Orange Prize for Fiction 2012, was shortlisted for the Stonewall Writer of the Year 2012, was an instant New York Times bestseller, and was translated into twenty-five languages. Miller holds an MA in Classics from Brown University, and she taught Latin, Greek and Shakespeare to high school students for over a decade. She lives outside Philadelphia.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Science Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE.
            In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child - not powerful and terrible, like her father, nor gorgeous and mercenary like her mother. Scorned and rejected, Circe grows up in the shadows, at home in neither the world of gods or mortals. But Circe has a dark power of her own: witchcraft. When her gift threatens the gods, she is banished to the island of Aiaia where she hones her occult craft, casting spells, gathering strange herbs and taming wild beasts. Yet a woman who stands alone will never be left in peace for long - and among her island's guests is an unexpected visitor: the mortal Odysseus, for whom Circe will risk everything.
            So Circe sets forth her tale, a vivid, mesmerizing epic of family rivalry, love and loss - the defiant, inextinguishable song of woman burning hot and bright through the darkness of a man's world.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.26/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>356</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2019-04-24</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Bloomsbury Publishing PLC</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10> 1408890046</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781408890042</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>81</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/4088/9781408890042.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Central and Eastern European Art Since 1950 (World of Art)</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>CEEASWA</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Maja Fowkes &amp; Reuben Fowkes</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Maja Fowkes and Reuben Fowkes are curators and art historian with a focus on the theory and aesthetics of Eastern European art from the socialist era to the present. They are co-directors of the Translocal Institute for Contemporary Art, a research centre in Budapest that operates at the intersection between ecological thought and contemporary art. </authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Art &amp; Photography </categorie>
        <bookSummary>In this path-breaking new history, Maja and Reuben Fowkes introduce outstanding artworks and major figures from across central and eastern Europe to reveal the movements, theories and styles that have shaped artistic practice since 1950. They emphasize the particularly rich and varied art scenes of Poland, Czechoslovakia, Hungary and Yugoslavia, extending their gaze at intervals to East Germany, Romania, the Baltic states and the rest of the Balkans.While politics in the region have been marked by unstable geography and dramatic transitions, artists have forged a path of persistent experiment and innovation. This generously illustrated overview explores the richness of their singular contribution to recent art history. Tracing art-historical changes from the short-lived unison of the socialist realist period to the incredible diversity of art in the post-communist era, the authors examine the repercussions of political events on artistic life - notably the uprisings in Hungary and Czechoslovakia, the Solidarity movement in Poland, and the collapse of the communist bloc. But their primary interest is in the experimental art of the neo-avant-garde that resisted official agendas and engaged with global currents such as performance art, video, multimedia and net art.</bookSummary>
        <rating>0/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>232</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-04-14</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Thames Hudson Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0500204373</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780500204375</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>160410</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/5002/9780500204375.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Abstract Art (World of Art)</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>AAWA</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Anna Moszynska</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Anna Moszynska pioneered the study of contemporary art at Sotheby's Institute during the late 1980s, and oversaw the development of the MA in Contemporary Art. In addition to writing books she has contributed to journals including Tate, Apollo, Arts Review, TLS and Art Monthly. Moszynska is an art critic for BBC Radio 3 and a member of the International Art Critics Association.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Art &amp; Photography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Since the early years of the 20th century, Western abstract art has fascinated, outraged and bewildered audiences. Its path to acceptance within the artistic mainstream was slow. Anna Moszynska traces the origins and evolution of abstract art, placing it in broad cultural context. She examines the pioneering work of Kandinsky, Malevich and Mondrian alongside the Russian Constructivists, the De Stijl group and the Bauhaus artists, contrasting European geometric abstraction in the 1930s and 40s with the emphasis on personal expression after the Second World War. Op, Kinetic and Minimal art of the postwar period is discussed and illustrated in detail, and new chapters bring the account up to date, exploring the crisis in abstraction of the 1980s and its revival - in paint, fabric, sculpture and installation - in recent decades. The first edition of this book, published in 1990, was acclaimed by reviewers; now in full colour and comprehensively revised, it will serve as the best introduction to abstract art for a new generation</bookSummary>
        <rating>5/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>272</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-04-14</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0500204454</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780500204450</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>94012</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/5002/9780500204450.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Too Much and Never Enough : How My Family Created the World's Most Dangerous Man</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TMNEHMFCWMDM</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Mary L. Trump</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Mary L. Trump holds a PhD from the Derner Institute of Advanced Psychological Studies and taught graduate courses in trauma, psychopathology and developmental psychology. She lives with her daughter in New York.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>In this revelatory, authoritative portrait of Donald J. Trump and the toxic family that made him, Mary L. Trump, a trained clinical psychologist and Donald's only niece, shines a bright light on the dark history of their family in order to explain how her uncle became the man who now threatens the world's health, economic security and social fabric.Mary Trump spent much of her childhood in her grandparents' large, imposing house in New York, where Donald and his four siblings grew up. She describes a nightmare of traumas, destructive relationships and a tragic combination of neglect and abuse. She explains how specific events and general family patterns created the damaged man who currently occupies the Oval Office, including the strange and harmful relationship between Fred Trump and his two oldest sons, Fred Jr. and Donald.A first-hand witness, Mary brings an incisive wit and unexpected humour to sometimes grim, often confounding family events. She recounts in unsparing detail everything from her uncle Donald's place in the family spotlight and Ivana's penchant for regifting to her grandmother's frequent injuries and illnesses and the appalling way Donald, Fred Trump's favourite son, dismissed and derided him when he began to succumb to Alzheimer's.Numerous pundits, armchair psychologists and journalists have sought to explain Donald Trump's lethal flaws. Mary Trump has the education, insight and intimate familiarity needed to reveal what makes Donald, and the rest of her clan, tick. She alone can recount this fascinating, unnerving saga, not just because of her insider's perspective but also because she is the only Trump willing to tell the truth about one of the world's most powerful and dysfunctional families.</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.93/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>240</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-07-28</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Simon &amp; Schuster Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1471190145</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781471190148</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>1536</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/4711/9781471190131.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>A Game of Thrones : Book 1 of A Song of Ice and Fire</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>GOTBAIF</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>George R. R. Martin</authorName>
            <authorDescription>George R.R. Martin is the author of fourteen novels, including five volumes of A SONG OF ICE AND FIRE, several collections of short stories and numerous screen plays for television drama and feature films. He lives in Santa Fe, New Mexico</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>The first volume of A Song of Ice and Fire, the greatest fantasy epic of the modern age. GAME OF THRONES is now a major TV series from HBO, starring Sean Bean. Summers span decades. Winter can last a lifetime. And the struggle for the Iron Throne has begun. As Warden of the north, Lord Eddard Stark counts it a curse when King Robert bestows on him the office of the Hand. His honour weighs him down at court where a true man does what he will, not what he must ...and a dead enemy is a thing of beauty. The old gods have no power in the south, Stark's family is split and there is treachery at court. Worse, the vengeance-mad heir of the deposed Dragon King has grown to maturity in exile in the Free Cities. He claims the Iron Throne.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.44/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>864</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2009-03-01</publicationDate>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>000647988X</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780006479888</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>3539</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/0064/9780006479888.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>A Storm of Swords: Part 1 Steel and Snow</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>SOSSAS</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>George R. R. Martin</authorName>
            <authorDescription>George R.R. Martin is the author of fourteen novels, including five volumes of A SONG OF ICE AND FIRE, several collections of short stories and numerous screen plays for television drama and feature films. He lives in Santa Fe, New Mexico</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>The third volume, part one of A Song of Ice and Fire, the greatest fantasy epic of the modern age. GAME OF THRONES is now a major TV series from HBO, featuring a stellar cast.Winter approaches Westeros like an angry beast.The Seven Kingdoms are divided by revolt and blood feud. In the northern wastes, a horde of hungry, savage people steeped in the dark magic of the wilderness is poised to invade the Kingdom of the North where Robb Stark wears his new-forged crown. And Robb's defences are ranged against the South, the land of the cunning and cruel Lannisters, who have his younger sisters in their power.Throughout Westeros, the war for the Iron Throne rages more fiercely than ever, but if the Wall is breached, no king will live to claim it.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.45/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>688</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2011-08-09</publicationDate>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0006479901</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780006479901</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>109547</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/0064/9780006479901.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
</bookdepository>
