<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<bookdepository>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Fast Exercise</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>FE</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dr Michael Mosley</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Dr Michael Mosley trained as a doctor before becoming a journalist and television presenter. He is the author of The Fast Diet, The 8-Week Blood Sugar Diet, The Clever Guts Diet and The Fast 800. He is married with four children. Dr Michael Mosley trained as a doctor before becoming a journalist and television presenter. He is the author of The Fast Diet, The 8-Week Blood Sugar Diet, The Clever Guts Diet and The Fast 800. He is married with four children.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fitness &amp; Diet</categorie>
        <bookSummary> The simple secret of high intensity training: get fitter, stronger and better toned in just a few minutes a day</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.79/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>208</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-12-19</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Short Books Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1780721986</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>781780721989</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>22679</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/7807/9781780721989.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Fast 800 Recipe Book</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TF800RB</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dr Clare Bailey</authorName>
            <authorDescription>DR CLARE BAILEY, wife of Michael Mosley, is a GP who has supported hundreds of patients to lose weight, reduce their blood sugars and put their diabetes into remission at her surgery in Buckinghamshire. She is the author of the bestselling 8-Week Blood Sugar Diet Recipe Book and Clever Guts Diet Recipe Book. JUSTINE PATTISON is one of the UK&apos;s leading healthy-eating recipe writers. She has published numerous books, makes regular appearances on television, can often be heard on the radio and contributes to many top magazines, newspapers and websites.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fitness &amp; Diet</categorie>
        <bookSummary> Low-carb, Mediterranean style recipes for intermittent fasting and long-term health </bookSummary>
        <rating>4.34/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>256</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2019-01-13</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Short Books Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1780724136</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781780724133</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>405</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/7807/9781780724133.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Hummus where the heart is</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>HWHI</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dunja Gulin</authorName>
            <authorDescription>For almost a decade Dunja has worked as a cooking teacher and chef - both on retreats and for private clients - and contributed to several healthy cookbooks. She also runs her own fermented food workshops. Dunja is the author of a popular book on vegan breakfast published in her native Croatia, and of The Vegan Baker, Raw Food Kitchen, The Vegan Pantry and Falafel Forever for RPS.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>General Cookery</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Rich, creamy and against all odds healthy, just a smear of this flavor-packed dip can transform any dish into something infinitely more delicious. Hummus-lovers everywhere will be satiated with this book of over 65 inventive vegan hummus recipes.</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.6/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>128</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2018-03-13</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Ryland, Peters &amp; Small Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1849759286</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781849759281</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>301490</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/8497/9781849759281.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Black Butler, Vol. 1</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>BBV1</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName> Yana Toboso</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Yana Toboso is the creator of the wildly popular series BLACK BUTLER which is currently serialized in Square Enix&apos;s magazine MONTHLY GFantasy. Her previous work was a single volume entitled RUST BLASTER.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Graphic Novels, Anime &amp; Manga</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Just a stone&apos;s throw from London lies the manor house of the illustrious Phantomhive earldom, its master one Ciel Phantomhive. Earl Phantomhive is a giant in the world of commerce, Queen Victoria&apos;s faithful servant . . . and a slip of a twelve-year old boy. Fortunately, his loyal butler, Sebastian, is ever at his side, ready to carry out the young master&apos;s wishes. And whether Sebastian is called to save a dinner party gone awry or probe the dark secrets of London&apos;s underbelly, there is practically nothing Sebastian cannot do. In fact, one might even say Sebastian is too good to be true . . . or at least, he is too good to be human . . .</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.36/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>192</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2010-01-26</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Little, Brown &amp; Company</publisher>
        <locationCity>New York</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United States</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0316080845</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780316080842</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>3724</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/3160/9780316080842.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>your name. The Official Visual Guide</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>YNOVG</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Makoto Shinkai</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Makoto Shinkai is a director, manga artist, and a writer known for works such as your name., The Garden of Words, and 5 Centimeters Per Second.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Graphic Novels, Anime &amp; Manga</categorie>
        <bookSummary>This story guide for Makoto
                    Shinkai&apos;s hit your name. features beautiful scenes from the film, along
                    with background art, character and concept art, storyboards, and a variety of
                    exclusive interviews from the people who brought Mitsuha and Taki&apos;s story to
                    life!</bookSummary>
        <rating>3/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>128</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-12-29</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Little, Brown &amp; Company</publisher>
        <locationCity>New York</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United States</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1975358716</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781975358716</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>778683</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/mid/9781/9753/9781975358716.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Flag : The Story of Revd David Railton Mc and the Tomb of the Unknown Warrior</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TFTRDRUW</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Andrew Richards</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Andrew Richards served 22 years with the Household Cavalry. During his last years of service, he graduated from the Open University with a Bachelor of Arts degree with Honours in Humanities with History and Classical Studies. Since retiring from the Army, he has written both fiction and non-fiction titles. His first non-fiction book, The Flag, was published by Casemate in 2016. He lives in New York with his wife and children.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography: Historical, Political &amp; Military</categorie>
        <bookSummary>This book describes the wartime experiences of Reverend David Railton, MC, who was a chaplain on the Western Front during WWI. As a chaplain, Railton supported soldiers in their worst moments, he buried the fallen, comforted the wounded, wrote to the families of the missing and killed, and helped the survivors to remember and mark the loss of their comrades so that they were able to move on and do their job. He was present at many battles, and received the Military Cross for rescuing an officer and two men under heavy fire on the Somme.</bookSummary>
        <rating>5/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>320</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2019-12-19</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Casemate Publishers</publisher>
        <locationCity></locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United States</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>161200749X</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781612007496</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>368914</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/6120/9781612007496.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Last Stop Auschwitz : My story of survival from within the camp</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>LSAMSSC</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Eddy de Wind</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Eddy de Wind (1916-87) was the last Jewish doctor to graduate from Leiden University in the Netherlands during World War Two. He was transported to Auschwitz in 1943. Following the camp&apos;s liberation in January 1945, De Wind returned to Holland and specialized as a psychiatrist and psychoanalyst. In 1949 he published &apos;Confrontation with Death&apos;, his famous article in which he introduced the idea of concentration-camp syndrome. Last Stop Auschwitz was published in Dutch in February 1946 and in English for the first time in 2020. It is the only complete book written in Auschwitz itself.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography: Historical, Political &amp; Military</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Eddy de Wind, a Dutch doctor and psychiatrist, was shipped to Auschwitz with his wife Friedel, whom he had met and married at the Westerbork labour camp in the Netherlands. At Auschwitz, they made it through the brutal selection process and were put to work. Each day, each hour became a battle for survival.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.04/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>272</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-01-09</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Transworld Publishers Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0857526839</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780857526830</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>93396</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/8575/9780857526847.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>War Doctor : Surgery on the Front Line</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>WCSFL</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>David Nott</authorName>
            <authorDescription>David Nott is a Welsh consultant surgeon, specializing in general and vascular surgery. He works mainly in London hospitals, but for more than twenty-five years he has also volunteered to work in disaster and war zones. He was appointed an Officer of the Order of the British Empire in the 2012 Birthday Honours and in 2016 he received the Robert Burns Humanitarian Award and the Pride of Britain Award. He lives in London with his wife and two daughters. War Doctor is his first book.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography: Historical, Political &amp; Military</categorie>
        <bookSummary>For more than twenty-five years, David Nott has taken unpaid leave from his job as a general and vascular surgeon with the NHS to volunteer in some of the world&apos;s most dangerous war zones. From Sarajevo under siege in 1993, to clandestine hospitals in rebel-held eastern Aleppo, he has carried out life-saving operations and field surgery in the most challenging conditions, and with none of the resources of a major London teaching hospital.
        The conflicts he has worked in form a chronology of twenty-first-century combat: Afghanistan, Sierra Leone, Liberia, Darfur, Congo, Iraq, Yemen, Libya, Gaza and Syria. But he has also volunteered in areas blighted by natural disasters, such as the earthquakes in Haiti and Nepal.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.57/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>320</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-01-09</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Pan MacMillan</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1509837051</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781509837052</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>2927</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/5098/9781509837052.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Little Book of Mindfulness : 10 minutes a day to less stress, more peace</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TLBM10DSMP</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dr Patrizia Collard</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Dr Patrizia Collard is a psychotherapist, mindfulness teacher, stress management consultant and lecturer in psychotherapy at the University of East London. Her books include Journey into Mindfulness, Mindfulness-based Cognitive Behavioural Therapy for Dummies and Awakening the Compassionate Mind (2014).</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Health Books</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Dr Patrizia Collard will show you how to bring simple 5- and 10-minute practices into your day in order to free yourself from stress and, ultimately, find more peace in your life.
            This beautifully illustrated book will set you and your family on the road of mindfulness so you can lead a more mindful, peaceful and relaxed life. Find long-lasting happiness with The Little Book of Mindfulness!</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.79/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>96</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2014-05-27</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Octopus Publishing Group</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1856753530</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781856753531</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>662</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/8567/9781856753531.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Wim Hof Method : Activate Your Potential, Transcend Your Limits</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TWHMAYPTYL</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Wim Hof</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Wim Hof, a.k.a. &apos;The Iceman,&apos; holds multiple world records for his feats of endurance and exposure to cold. The benefits of his method, now practiced by tens of thousands, have been validated by eight university research studies. He has been featured on the BBC, VICE Media, and the Discovery Channel; The Joe Rogan Experience, The Tim Ferriss Show, and The School of Greatness podcasts; and in the bestselling book What Doesn&apos;t Kill Us by Scott Carney. He lives in the Netherlands with his family.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Health Books</categorie>
        <bookSummary>In The Wim Hof Method, this trailblazer of human potential shares his simple three-pillar approach that anyone can use to improve health and performance - and see real results within just a few days. Refined over forty years and championed by scientists across the globe, you&apos;ll learn how to harness three key elements of Cold, Breathing and Mindset to master mind over matter and achieve the impossible.</bookSummary>
        <rating>0/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>224</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-09-24</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Ebury Publishing</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1846046297</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781846046292</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>126</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/8460/9781846046292.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Good Vibes, Good Life : How Self-Love Is the Key to Unlocking Your Greatness</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>GVGLHSLKUG</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Vex King</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Vex King is a social media influencer, writer, mind coach and lifestyle entrepreneur. Vex experienced many challenges when he was growing up: his father died when Vex was just a baby, his family were often homeless and he grew up in troubled neighbourhoods where he regularly experienced racism. Despite this, Vex successfully turned his whole life around, and through his popular Instagram account (@vexking) has become a source of inspiration for thousands of young people. He started the Good Vibes Only #GVO movement to help others use the power of positivity to transform themselves and their lives into something greater. www.vexking.com</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Health Books</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Vex overcame adversity to become a source of hope for thousands of young people, and now draws from his personal experience and his intuitive wisdom to inspire you to:
            - practise self-care, overcome toxic energy and prioritize your wellbeing
            - cultivate positive lifestyle habits, including mindfulness and meditation
            - change your beliefs to invite great opportunities into your life
            - manifest your goals using tried-and-tested techniques
            - overcome fear and flow with the Universe
            - find your higher purpose and become a shining light for others
            With additional messages and brand new illustrations, this new gift edition of Good Vibes, Good Life will empower and inspire you to change the way you feel, think, speak, act and live your life.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.21/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>304</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2018-12-04</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Hay House UK Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1788171829</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781788171823</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>72</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/mid/9781/7881/9781788171823.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>1984</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>NINETEENEIGHTYFOUR</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>George Orwell</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Eric Arthur Blair (1903-1950), better known by his pen-name, George Orwell, was born in India, where his father worked for the Civil Service. An author and journalist, Orwell was one of the most prominent and influential figures in twentieth-century literature. His unique political allegory Animal Farm was published in 1945, and it was this novel, together with the dystopia of Nineteen Eighty-Four (1949), which brought him world-wide fame. His novels and non-fiction include Burmese Days, Down and Out in Paris and London, The Road to Wigan Pier and Homage to Catalonia.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Science Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Renowned urban artist Shepard Fairey&apos;s new look for Orwell&apos;s dystopian masterpiece
            Winston Smith works for the Ministry of Truth in London, chief city of Airstrip One. Big Brother stares out from every poster, the Thought Police uncover every act of betrayal. When Winston finds love with Julia, he discovers that life does not have to be dull and deadening, and awakens to new possibilities. Despite the police helicopters that hover and circle overhead, Winston and Julia begin to question the Party; they are drawn towards conspiracy. Yet Big Brother will not tolerate dissent - even in the mind. For those with original thoughts they invented Room 101. . .
            1984 is George Orwell&apos;s terrifying vision of a totalitarian future in which everything and everyone is slave to a tyrannical regime.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.18/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>336</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2008-10-01</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Penguin Books Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0141036141</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780141036144</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>5</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/1410/9780141036144.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Circe</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>CIRCE</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Madeline Millert</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Madeline Miller is the author of The Song of Achilles, which won the Orange Prize for Fiction 2012, was shortlisted for the Stonewall Writer of the Year 2012, was an instant New York Times bestseller, and was translated into twenty-five languages. Miller holds an MA in Classics from Brown University, and she taught Latin, Greek and Shakespeare to high school students for over a decade. She lives outside Philadelphia.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Science Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE.
            In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child - not powerful and terrible, like her father, nor gorgeous and mercenary like her mother. Scorned and rejected, Circe grows up in the shadows, at home in neither the world of gods or mortals. But Circe has a dark power of her own: witchcraft. When her gift threatens the gods, she is banished to the island of Aiaia where she hones her occult craft, casting spells, gathering strange herbs and taming wild beasts. Yet a woman who stands alone will never be left in peace for long - and among her island&apos;s guests is an unexpected visitor: the mortal Odysseus, for whom Circe will risk everything.
            So Circe sets forth her tale, a vivid, mesmerizing epic of family rivalry, love and loss - the defiant, inextinguishable song of woman burning hot and bright through the darkness of a man&apos;s world.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.26/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>356</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2019-04-24</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Bloomsbury Publishing PLC</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10> 1408890046</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781408890042</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>81</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/4088/9781408890042.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Dune</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>DUNE</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Frank Herbert</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Frank Herbert was born in 1920. His colourful and varied career included stints as a radio news commentator and jungle survival instructor. He is best known for creating the world of DUNE, which established Frank Herbert as a master of modern science fiction. He died in 1986.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Science Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Before The Matrix, before Star Wars, before Ender&apos;s Game and Neuromancer, there was Dune: winner of the prestigious Hugo and Nebula awards, and widely considered one of the greatest science fiction novels ever written.
                Melange, or &apos;spice&apos;, is the most valuable - and rarest - element in the universe; a drug that does everything from increasing a person&apos;s life-span to making intersteller travel possible. And it can only be found on a single planet: the inhospitable desert world Arrakis.
                Whoever controls Arrakis controls the spice. And whoever controls the spice controls the universe.
                When the Emperor transfers stewardship of Arrakis from the noble House Harkonnen to House Atreides, the Harkonnens fight back, murdering Duke Leto Atreides. Paul, his son, and Lady Jessica, his concubine, flee into the desert. On the point of death, they are rescued by a band for Fremen, the native people of Arrakis, who control Arrakis&apos; second great resource: the giant worms that burrow beneath the burning desert sands.
                In order to avenge his father and retake Arrakis from the Harkonnens, Paul must earn the trust of the Fremen and lead a tiny army against the innumerable forces aligned against them.
                And his journey will change the universe.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.22/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>592</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2015-07-23</publicationDate>
        <publisher>HODDER &amp; STOUGHTON</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0340960191</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>780340960196</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>18</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/3409/9780340960196.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Central and Eastern European Art Since 1950 (World of Art)</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>CEEASWA</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Maja Fowkes &amp; Reuben Fowkes</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Maja Fowkes and Reuben Fowkes are curators and art historian with a focus on the theory and aesthetics of Eastern European art from the socialist era to the present. They are co-directors of the Translocal Institute for Contemporary Art, a research centre in Budapest that operates at the intersection between ecological thought and contemporary art. </authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Art &amp; Photography </categorie>
        <bookSummary>In this path-breaking new history, Maja and Reuben Fowkes introduce outstanding artworks and major figures from across central and eastern Europe to reveal the movements, theories and styles that have shaped artistic practice since 1950. They emphasize the particularly rich and varied art scenes of Poland, Czechoslovakia, Hungary and Yugoslavia, extending their gaze at intervals to East Germany, Romania, the Baltic states and the rest of the Balkans.While politics in the region have been marked by unstable geography and dramatic transitions, artists have forged a path of persistent experiment and innovation. This generously illustrated overview explores the richness of their singular contribution to recent art history. Tracing art-historical changes from the short-lived unison of the socialist realist period to the incredible diversity of art in the post-communist era, the authors examine the repercussions of political events on artistic life - notably the uprisings in Hungary and Czechoslovakia, the Solidarity movement in Poland, and the collapse of the communist bloc. But their primary interest is in the experimental art of the neo-avant-garde that resisted official agendas and engaged with global currents such as performance art, video, multimedia and net art.</bookSummary>
        <rating>0/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>232</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-04-14</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Thames Hudson Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0500204373</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780500204375</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>160410</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/5002/9780500204375.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Abstract Art (World of Art)</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>AAWA</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Anna Moszynska</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Anna Moszynska pioneered the study of contemporary art at Sotheby&apos;s Institute during the late 1980s, and oversaw the development of the MA in Contemporary Art. In addition to writing books she has contributed to journals including Tate, Apollo, Arts Review, TLS and Art Monthly. Moszynska is an art critic for BBC Radio 3 and a member of the International Art Critics Association.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Art &amp; Photography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Since the early years of the 20th century, Western abstract art has fascinated, outraged and bewildered audiences. Its path to acceptance within the artistic mainstream was slow. Anna Moszynska traces the origins and evolution of abstract art, placing it in broad cultural context. She examines the pioneering work of Kandinsky, Malevich and Mondrian alongside the Russian Constructivists, the De Stijl group and the Bauhaus artists, contrasting European geometric abstraction in the 1930s and 40s with the emphasis on personal expression after the Second World War. Op, Kinetic and Minimal art of the postwar period is discussed and illustrated in detail, and new chapters bring the account up to date, exploring the crisis in abstraction of the 1980s and its revival - in paint, fabric, sculpture and installation - in recent decades. The first edition of this book, published in 1990, was acclaimed by reviewers; now in full colour and comprehensively revised, it will serve as the best introduction to abstract art for a new generation</bookSummary>
        <rating>5/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>272 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-04-14</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Thames &amp; Hudson Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0500204454</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780500204450</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>94012</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/5002/9780500204450.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Adobe Photoshop CC Classroom in a Book</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>APCCCB</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Andrew Faulkner</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Andrew Faulkner is the founder and creative guru at Afstudio Design with 20+ years in providing design and photo-illustration services to a long list of corporate clients. His work with Adobe Systems started in 1994, when they invited him to help develop the first Adobe Classroom in a Book. Andrew has co-authored numerous editions of the Classroom in a Book series on Photoshop, After Effects, and Flash. In addition to his graphic design work, he is a veteran Photoshop jockey, and his digital collage illustration work has been featured in The Wall Street Journal, The New York Times, The LA Times, and The Washington Post. His recent digital painting work can be seen online at www.andrew-faulkner.com. When Andrew&apos;s not at the studio, you can probably find him hunting down rare vinyl at one of the Bay Area&apos;s vintage record stores.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <author>
            <authorName>Conrad Chavez</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Conrad Chavez has provided education, training, and support for digital-media applications for over 20 years, originally contributing countless pages to the user guides for print, Web, and digital video products at Aldus Corporation and Adobe Systems Inc. Now a freelance writer and editor, Conrad creates books and videos that teach Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Creative Cloud workflows. His work includes the last three editions of Real World Adobe Photoshop for Photographers and the video Color Management for Photographers and Designers. He also writes articles for publications including CreativePro.com, InDesign Magazine, and Peachpit.com. To learn more about Conrad&apos;s work and photography, please see www.conradchavez.com.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Art &amp; Photography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Creative professionals seeking the fastest, easiest, most comprehensive way to learn Adobe Photoshop choose Adobe Photoshop CC Classroom in a Book (2019 release) from Adobe Press. The 15 project-based lessons show key step-by-step techniques for working in Photoshop, including how to correct, enhance, and distort digital images, create image composites, and prepare images for print and the web.In addition to learning the essential elements of the Photoshop interface, this revised edition for the 2019 release covers features like the new Frame tool, designing reflected and radial art with Paint Symmetry, correcting mistakes with updated Undo, Navigating the redesigned Home screen, removing objects with upgraded Content-Aware Fill, saving time with simplified editing and transformations, and much more!The online companion files include all the necessary assets for readers to complete the projects featured in each chapter. All buyers of the book get full access to the Web Edition: A Web-based version of the complete ebook enhanced with video and multiple-choice quizzes.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.31/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber> 416 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2019-01-10</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Pearson Education (US)</publisher>
        <locationCity>Boston</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United States</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0135261783</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780135261781</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>17156</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/1352/9780135261781.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Stone Cold : The Extraordinary Story of Len Opie, Australia&apos;s Deadliest Soldier</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>SCTESLOADS</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Andrew Faulkner</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Andrew Faulkner is the founder and creative guru at Afstudio Design with 20+ years in providing design and photo-illustration services to a long list of corporate clients. His work with Adobe Systems started in 1994, when they invited him to help develop the first Adobe Classroom in a Book. Andrew has co-authored numerous editions of the Classroom in a Book series on Photoshop, After Effects, and Flash. In addition to his graphic design work, he is a veteran Photoshop jockey, and his digital collage illustration work has been featured in The Wall Street Journal, The New York Times, The LA Times, and The Washington Post. His recent digital painting work can be seen online at www.andrew-faulkner.com. When Andrew&apos;s not at the studio, you can probably find him hunting down rare vinyl at one of the Bay Area&apos;s vintage record stores.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>&apos;If I&apos;d have been a Vietcong you&apos;d be dead.&apos; - Len Opie. &apos;Len was a soldier above soldiers.&apos; - Keith Payne VC. Through three wars across 30 years, Len Opie carved a reputation as one of the country&apos;s greatest infantrymen. A cold-eyed killer who drank nothing stronger than weak tea, he fought with his bare hands, a sharpened shovel and piano wire. He was a larrikin who went by the book, unless the book was wrong. He set his own bar high and expected others to do the same.Stone Cold is the extraordinary story of one of Australia&apos;s most fearless fighters. It takes us into the jungles of New Guinea and Borneo and some of the fiercest battles of World War II. It goes to the cold heart of Korea, where Len emerged from the ranks to excel in the epic Battle of Kapyong and play a key role at the Battle of Maryang San. And it drops us into the centre of the American counterinsurgency war in Vietnam with Len&apos;s involvement in the CIA&apos;s shadowy black ops program, Phoenix.Action-packed and surprising, Stone Cold gives rich life to a warrior soldier and one of Australia&apos;s greatest diggers.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.11/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber> 320 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2016-10-11</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Allen  &amp; Unwin</publisher>
        <locationCity>St Leonards</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>Australia</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>174237378X</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781742373782</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>250242</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/7423/9781742373782.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Too Much and Never Enough : How My Family Created the World&apos;s Most Dangerous Man</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TMNEHMFCWMDM</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Mary L. Trump</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Mary L. Trump holds a PhD from the Derner Institute of Advanced Psychological Studies and taught graduate courses in trauma, psychopathology and developmental psychology. She lives with her daughter in New York.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>In this revelatory, authoritative portrait of Donald J. Trump and the toxic family that made him, Mary L. Trump, a trained clinical psychologist and Donald&apos;s only niece, shines a bright light on the dark history of their family in order to explain how her uncle became the man who now threatens the world&apos;s health, economic security and social fabric.Mary Trump spent much of her childhood in her grandparents&apos; large, imposing house in New York, where Donald and his four siblings grew up. She describes a nightmare of traumas, destructive relationships and a tragic combination of neglect and abuse. She explains how specific events and general family patterns created the damaged man who currently occupies the Oval Office, including the strange and harmful relationship between Fred Trump and his two oldest sons, Fred Jr. and Donald.A first-hand witness, Mary brings an incisive wit and unexpected humour to sometimes grim, often confounding family events. She recounts in unsparing detail everything from her uncle Donald&apos;s place in the family spotlight and Ivana&apos;s penchant for regifting to her grandmother&apos;s frequent injuries and illnesses and the appalling way Donald, Fred Trump&apos;s favourite son, dismissed and derided him when he began to succumb to Alzheimer&apos;s.Numerous pundits, armchair psychologists and journalists have sought to explain Donald Trump&apos;s lethal flaws. Mary Trump has the education, insight and intimate familiarity needed to reveal what makes Donald, and the rest of her clan, tick. She alone can recount this fascinating, unnerving saga, not just because of her insider&apos;s perspective but also because she is the only Trump willing to tell the truth about one of the world&apos;s most powerful and dysfunctional families.</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.93/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>240 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-07-28</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Simon &amp; Schuster Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>1471190145</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9781471190148</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>1536</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9781/4711/9781471190131.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Everything I Know About Love</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>EIKAL</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dolly Alderton</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Dolly Alderton is an award-winning author and journalist. She is a columnist for The Sunday Times Style and has also written for GQ, Red, Marie Claire and Grazia. She co-hosts the weekly pop-culture and current affairs podcast The High Low alongside journalist Pandora Sykes. Her first book Everything I Know About Love became a top five Sunday Times bestseller in its first week of publication and won a National Book Award for Autobiography of the Year. Her first novel Ghosts will be published by Fig Tree/Penguin in October 2020.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Biography</categorie>
        <bookSummary>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER WITH A NEW CHAPTER ON TURNING THIRTY &apos;There is no writer quite like Dolly Alderton working today and very soon the world will know it&apos; Lisa Taddeo, author Three Women &apos;The book we will thrust into our friends&apos; hands. Alderton feels like a best friend and your older sister all rolled into one and her pages wrap around you like a warm hug&apos; Evening Standard Award-winning journalist Dolly Alderton survived her twenties (just about) and in Everything I Know About Love, she gives an unflinching account of the bad dates and squalid flat-shares, the heartaches and humiliations, and most importantly, the unbreakable female friendships that helped her to hold it all together. Glittering with wit, heart and humour, this is a book to press into the hands of every woman who has ever been there or is about to find themselves taking that first step towards the rest of their lives. &apos;Alderton is Nora Ephron for the millennial generation&apos; Elizabeth Day &apos;Steeped in furiously funny accounts of one-night stands, ill-advised late-night taxi journeys up the M1, grubby flat-shares and the beauty of female friendships, as Alderton joyfully booze-cruises her way through her twenties&apos; Metro &apos;Deeply funny, sometimes shocking, and admirably open-hearted and optimistic&apos; Daily Telegraph &apos;A sensitive, astute and funny account of growing up millennial&apos; Observer &apos;I loved its truth, self awareness, humour and most of all, its heart-spilling generosity&apos; Sophie Dahl &apos;Alderton proves a razor-sharp observer of the shifting dynamics of long term female friendship&apos; Mail on Sunday &apos;It&apos;s so full of life and laughs - I gobbled up this book. Alderton has built something beautiful and true out of many fragments of daftness&apos; Amy Liptrot *Winner of Autobiography of the Year at the National Book Awards 2018* *A Waterstones Paperback of the Year 2019* *A Sunday Times paperback of the year 2019* *Selected for Stylist&apos;s The Decade&apos;s 15 Best Books by Remarkable Women*</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.19/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>368 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-09-21</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Penguin Books Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0241982103</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780241982105</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>804</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/2419/9780241982105.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Tale of Squirrel Nutkin</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TTSN</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Beatrix Potter</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Beatrix Potter is regarded as one of the world&apos;s best-loved children&apos;s authors of all time. From her first book, The Tale of Peter Rabbit, published by Frederick Warne in 1902, she went on to create a series of stories based around animal characters including Mrs. Tiggy-winkle, Benjamin Bunny, Jemima Puddle-duck, Mr. Jeremy Fisher and Tom Kitten. Her humorous, lively tales and beautiful illustrations have become a natural part of childhood. With revenue from the sales of her books, Beatrix Potter bought a farm - Hill Top - in the English Lake District, where she later became a farmer and prize-winning sheep breeder. She launched the now vast merchandise programme by patenting the very first Peter Rabbit doll in 1903. The product range continues to grow today with licences around the world including baby clothing and bedding, nursery decor products and collectables. Upon her death, Beatrix Potter left 14 farms and over 4000 acres of Lake District farmland to the National Trust so that the place that she loved would remain undeveloped and protected for future generations to enjoy. Today Beatrix Potter&apos;s original 23 tales are still published by Frederick Warne, alongside a wide range of other formats including baby books, activity books and gift and sound books.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Children&apos;s Books</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Tale of Squirrel Nutkin is an original classic by Beatrix Potter. Beatrix Potter&apos;s famous tale of a naughty squirrel who loses his tail is as popular today as it was when it was first published over 100 years ago. Join Nutkin, his brother Twinkleberry and all his cousins as they make their way over to Owl Island to gather nuts. See what happens when Old Brown, the terrifying owl guardian of the island decides he has had enough of silly Nutkin&apos;s cheekiness! Ouch!! </bookSummary>
        <rating>4/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>64 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2002-09-16</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Penguin Random House Children&apos;s UK</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0723247714</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780723247715</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>88782</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/7232/9780723247715.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Tale Of Peter Rabbit</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TTOPR</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Beatrix Potter</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Beatrix Potter is regarded as one of the world&apos;s best-loved children&apos;s authors of all time. From her first book, The Tale of Peter Rabbit, published by Frederick Warne in 1902, she went on to create a series of stories based around animal characters including Mrs. Tiggy-winkle, Benjamin Bunny, Jemima Puddle-duck, Mr. Jeremy Fisher and Tom Kitten. Her humorous, lively tales and beautiful illustrations have become a natural part of childhood. With revenue from the sales of her books, Beatrix Potter bought a farm - Hill Top - in the English Lake District, where she later became a farmer and prize-winning sheep breeder. She launched the now vast merchandise programme by patenting the very first Peter Rabbit doll in 1903. The product range continues to grow today with licences around the world including baby clothing and bedding, nursery decor products and collectables. Upon her death, Beatrix Potter left 14 farms and over 4000 acres of Lake District farmland to the National Trust so that the place that she loved would remain undeveloped and protected for future generations to enjoy. Today Beatrix Potter&apos;s original 23 tales are still published by Frederick Warne, alongside a wide range of other formats including baby books, activity books and gift and sound books.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Children&apos;s Books</categorie>
        <bookSummary>One of Beatrix Potter&apos;s most popular and well-loved tales, this mischievous little rabbit has hopped into the heart of generations of book lovers. Peter Rabbit loves the yummy vegetables he finds in Mr McGregor&apos;s garden, the only problem is: Mr McGregor doesn&apos;t want Peter to get his paws on his crops! First published in 1902, this edition has been re-originated so it matches Beatrix&apos;s first published work, all those years ago.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.18/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>80 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2002-09-16</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Penguin Random House Children&apos;s UK</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0723247706</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780723247708</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>5097</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/7232/9780723247708.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Famous Five: Five On A Treasure Island : Book 1</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>FFFTI</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Enid Blyton</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Enid Blyton&apos;s books have sold over 500 million copies and have been translated into other languages more often than any other children&apos;s author. She wrote over 700 books and about 2,000 short stories, including favourites such as The Famous Five,The Secret Seven, The Magic Faraway Tree, Malory Towers and Noddy. Born in London in 1897, Enid lived much of her life in Buckinghamshire and adored dogs, gardening and the countryside. She died in 1968 but remains one of the world&apos;s best-loved storytellers.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Children&apos;s Books</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Meet Julian, Dick, Anne, George and Timothy. Together they are THE FAMOUS FIVE - Enid Blyton&apos;s most popular adventure series. All 21 titles also available as audiobooks! &apos;There was something else out on the sea by the rocks - something dark that seemed to lurch out of the waves . . . What could it be?&apos; Julian, Dick and Anne are spending the holidays with their tomboy cousin George and her dog, Timothy. One day, George takes them to explore nearby Kirrin Island, with its rocky little coast and old ruined castle on the top. Over on the island, they make a thrilling discovery, which leads them deep into the dungeons of Kirrin Castle on a dangerous adventure. Who - and what - will they find there?</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.18/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>192 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>1997-03-19</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Hachette Children&apos;s Group</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0340681063</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780340681060</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>30712</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/3406/9780340681060.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Lost Ocean : An Inky Adventure &amp; Colouring Book</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>LOAIACB</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Johanna Basford</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Johanna Basford is the ink evangelist and creator of Secret Garden, Enchanted Forest, Lost Ocean, Magical Jungle, Johanna&apos;s Christmas and Ivy and the Inky Butterfly. Johanna&apos;s intricate, hand-drawn illustrations are loved by her many fans; to date she has sold over 21 million colouring books worldwide. Visit her online at johannabasford.com or follow @johannabasford.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Crafts &amp; Hobbies</categorie>
        <bookSummary>A beautiful new colouring book that takes you on a magical journey beneath the waves, from the creator of the worldwide bestsellers, Secret Garden and Enchanted Forest. Also features a large double-sided pull-out poster to colour and keep.With Lost Ocean, Johanna Basford invites colour-inners of all ages to discover an enchanting underwater world hidden within the depths of the sea.With intricate pen and ink illustrations to complete, colour and embellish, readers will meet shoals of exotic fish, curious octopuses and delicately penned seahorses, visit coral reefs and barnacle-studded shipwrecks, and discover intricate shells and pirate treasure. Secret Garden and Enchanted Forest fans and newcomers alike will delight in this creative journey into an inky new world.For Lost Ocean Johanna picked a crisp ivory paper that accentuates and complements your chosen colour palette. The smooth, untextured pages allows for beautiful blending or gradient techniques with coloured pencils, or are perfect for pens, allowing the nib to glide evenly over the surface without feathering.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.46/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>80</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>1997-03-19</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Ebury Publishing</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0753557150</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780753557150</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>7850</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/7535/9780753557150.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>200 Crochet Blocks for Blankets, Throws and Afghans : Crochet Squares to Mix-and-Match</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>CBBTACSMM</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Jan Eaton</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Jan Eaton is a needlecraft and textile designer. She has published many needlecraft books, including Country Crochet and Knitted Lace, and Crochet Basics.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Crafts &amp; Hobbies</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Crochet is one of the oldest and most fascinating ways of creating a fabric out of yarn. Find out how to create wonderful and unique afghans, wall hangings and accessories in a kaleidoscope of colourful contemporary and traditional designs. All stitches and techniques are clearly explained with step-by-step illustrations, from working in rows and in the round to joining blocks and making figures. At-a-glance symbols denote the methods used and level of difficulty, so both new and experienced crafters can easily create a crochet masterpiece.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.25/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>128</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2005-01-28</publicationDate>
        <publisher> DAVID &amp; CHARLES</publisher>
        <locationCity>Newton Abbot</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0715321412</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780715321416</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>28844</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/7153/9780715321416.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Star Wars Origami : 36 Amazing Paper-Folding Projects from a Galaxy Far, Far Away...</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>SWOAPFPGFFA</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Chris Alexander</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Chris Alexander began doing origami at the age of four. Since then he has created dozens of original designs, many of them Star Wars themed. He has a large Star Wars fan base and tours the country folding at conventions and museums. He lives in Lancaster, California.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Crafts &amp; Hobbies</categorie>
        <bookSummary>The power of the Force meets the joy of origami. Here is everything you need to create a galaxy of Star Wars characters, ships, droids, and weapons. The ingenious models are created by Chris Alexander, the master of Star Wars origami, and come with complete step-by-step directions as well as an introduction to origami definitions, symbols, and basic folds. Bound in the back is the book&apos;s unique folding paper, 72 sheets in all. Illustrated with meticulously detailed original art, the specially designed paper makes each creation - menacing Darth Sidious, confident Chewbacca, the Death Star, Yoda, and more - come alive.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.03/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>272</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2012-08-15</publicationDate>
        <publisher> Workman Publishing</publisher>
        <locationCity>New York</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United States</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0761169431</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780761169437</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>5595</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/7611/9780761169437.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Into the Water : The Sunday Times Bestseller</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>IWTTB</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName> Paula Hawkins</authorName>
            <authorDescription>PAULA HAWKINS worked as a journalist for fifteen years before turning her hand to fiction. Born and brought up in Zimbabwe, Paula moved to London in 1989 and has lived there ever since. Her first thriller, The Girl on the Train, has been a global phenomenon, selling almost 20 million copies worldwide. Published in over forty languages, it has been a No.1 bestseller around the world and was a No.1 box office hit film starring Emily Blunt. Into the Water is her second stand-alone thriller.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Crime &amp; Thriller</categorie>
        <bookSummary>The addictive new psychological thriller from the author of The Girl on the Train, the runaway Sunday Times No. 1 bestseller and global phenomenon.In the last days before her death, Nel called her sister. Jules didn&apos;t pick up the phone, ignoring her plea for help. Now Nel is dead. They say she jumped. And Jules has been dragged back to the one place she hoped she had escaped for good, to care for the teenage girl her sister left behind.But Jules is afraid. So afraid. Of her long-buried memories, of the old Mill House, of knowing that Nel would never have jumped.And most of all she&apos;s afraid of the water, and the place they call the Drowning Pool . . .With the same propulsive writing and acute understanding of human instincts that captivated millions of readers around the world in her explosive debut thriller, The Girl on the Train, Paula Hawkins delivers an urgent, satisfying read that hinges on the stories we tell about our pasts and their power to destroy the lives we live now.</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.57/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>368</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2017-05-17</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Transworld Publishers Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0857524437</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780857524430</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>82183</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/8575/9780857524430.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>The Girl on the Train</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>TGOTT</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName> Paula Hawkins</authorName>
            <authorDescription>PAULA HAWKINS worked as a journalist for fifteen years before turning her hand to fiction. Born and brought up in Zimbabwe, Paula moved to London in 1989 and has lived there ever since. Her first thriller, The Girl on the Train, has been a global phenomenon, selling almost 20 million copies worldwide. Published in over forty languages, it has been a No.1 bestseller around the world and was a No.1 box office hit film starring Emily Blunt. Into the Water, her second stand-alone thriller, has also been a global No.1 bestseller.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Crime &amp; Thriller</categorie>
        <bookSummary>THE RUNAWAY SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER AND THRILLER OF THE YEAR, NOW A MAJOR FILM STARRING EMILY BLUNT &apos;Really great suspense novel. Kept me up most of the night. The alcoholic narrator is dead perfect&apos; Rachel catches the same commuter train every morning. She knows it will wait at the same signal each time, overlooking a row of back gardens. She&apos;s even started to feel like she knows the people who live in one of the houses. &apos;Jess and Jason&apos;, she calls them. Their life - as she sees it - is perfect. If only Rachel could be that happy.And then she sees something shocking. It&apos;s only a minute until the train moves on, but it&apos;s enough.Now everything&apos;s changed. Now Rachel has a chance to become a part of the lives she&apos;s only watched from afar.Now they&apos;ll see; she&apos;s much more than just the girl on the train...</bookSummary>
        <rating>3.92/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>416</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2016-05-05</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Transworld Publishers Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0552779776</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780552779777</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>7339</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/5527/9780552779777.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>Ghosts : The Debut Novel from the Bestselling Author of Everything I Know About Love</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>GTDNFBAEIKAL</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>Dolly Alderton</authorName>
            <authorDescription>Dolly Alderton is an award-winning author and journalist. She is a columnist for The Sunday Times Style and has also written for GQ, Red, Marie Claire and Grazia. She co-hosts the weekly pop-culture and current affairs podcast The High Low alongside journalist Pandora Sykes. Her first book Everything I Know About Love became a top five Sunday Times bestseller in its first week of publication and won a National Book Award for Autobiography of the Year. Her first novel Ghosts will be published by Fig Tree/Penguin in October 2020.</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>Nina Dean has arrived at her early thirties as a successful food writer with loving friends and family, plus a new home and neighbourhood. When she meets Max, a beguiling romantic hero who tells her on date one that he&apos;s going to marry her, it feels like all is going to plan.A new relationship couldn&apos;t have come at a better time - her thirties have not been the liberating, uncomplicated experience she was sold. Everywhere she turns, she is reminded of time passing and opportunities dwindling. Friendships are fading, ex-boyfriends are moving on and, worse, everyone&apos;s moving to the suburbs. There&apos;s no solace to be found in her family, with a mum who&apos;s caught in a baffling mid-life makeover and a beloved dad who is vanishing in slow-motion into dementia. Dolly Alderton&apos;s debut novel is funny and tender, filled with whip-smart observations about relationships, family, memory, and how we live now.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.19/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>352</pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2020-10-15</publicationDate>
        <publisher>Penguin Books Ltd</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0241465338</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780241465332</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>33164</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/2414/9780241465332.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>A Game of Thrones : Book 1 of A Song of Ice and Fire</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>GOTBAIF</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>George R. R. Martin</authorName>
            <authorDescription>George R.R. Martin is the author of fourteen novels, including five volumes of A SONG OF ICE AND FIRE, several collections of short stories and numerous screen plays for television drama and feature films. He lives in Santa Fe, New Mexico</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>The first volume of A Song of Ice and Fire, the greatest fantasy epic of the modern age. GAME OF THRONES is now a major TV series from HBO, starring Sean Bean. Summers span decades. Winter can last a lifetime. And the struggle for the Iron Throne has begun. As Warden of the north, Lord Eddard Stark counts it a curse when King Robert bestows on him the office of the Hand. His honour weighs him down at court where a true man does what he will, not what he must ...and a dead enemy is a thing of beauty. The old gods have no power in the south, Stark&apos;s family is split and there is treachery at court. Worse, the vengeance-mad heir of the deposed Dragon King has grown to maturity in exile in the Free Cities. He claims the Iron Throne.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.44/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>864 </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2009-03-01</publicationDate>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>000647988X</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780006479888</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>3539</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/0064/9780006479888.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
    <book>
        <bookTitle>A Storm of Swords: Part 1 Steel and Snow</bookTitle>
        <bookInitials>SOSSAS</bookInitials>
        <author>
            <authorName>George R. R. Martin</authorName>
            <authorDescription>George R.R. Martin is the author of fourteen novels, including five volumes of A SONG OF ICE AND FIRE, several collections of short stories and numerous screen plays for television drama and feature films. He lives in Santa Fe, New Mexico</authorDescription>
        </author>
        <categorie>Fiction</categorie>
        <bookSummary>The third volume, part one of A Song of Ice and Fire, the greatest fantasy epic of the modern age. GAME OF THRONES is now a major TV series from HBO, featuring a stellar cast.Winter approaches Westeros like an angry beast.The Seven Kingdoms are divided by revolt and blood feud. In the northern wastes, a horde of hungry, savage people steeped in the dark magic of the wilderness is poised to invade the Kingdom of the North where Robb Stark wears his new-forged crown. And Robb&apos;s defences are ranged against the South, the land of the cunning and cruel Lannisters, who have his younger sisters in their power.Throughout Westeros, the war for the Iron Throne rages more fiercely than ever, but if the Wall is breached, no king will live to claim it.</bookSummary>
        <rating>4.45/5</rating>
        <pagesNumber>688  </pagesNumber>
        <publicationDate>2011-08-09</publicationDate>
        <publisher>HarperCollins Publishers</publisher>
        <locationCity>London</locationCity>
        <locationCountry>United Kingdom</locationCountry>
        <language>English</language>
        <ISBN10>0006479901</ISBN10>
        <ISBN13>9780006479901</ISBN13>
        <sellerRank>109547</sellerRank>
        <linkImg>https://d1w7fb2mkkr3kw.cloudfront.net/assets/images/book/lrg/9780/0064/9780006479901.jpg</linkImg>
    </book>
</bookdepository>